remakingjunecleaver.com 2018-12-30

# Privacy Policy |

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, fill out a form or enter a giveaway.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

– To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

– To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

– To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

– To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

We do not use cookies.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

### **COOKIE POLICY:**

Updated 5/22/2018

We use cookies on our sites (www.momskoop.com and the subdomains associated with www.momskoop.com) (“our site”) for a number of purposes. They help us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website, and also allow us to improve our site. By continuing to browse the site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies.

A cookie is a small file of letters and numbers that we store on your browser or the hard drive of your computer if you agree. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive.

**We use the following cookies:**

Strictly necessary cookies. These are cookies that are required for the operation of our website. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of our website, use a shopping cart or make use of the e-billing services.

Analytical/performance cookies. They allow us to recognize and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around our website when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way our website works, for example, by ensuring that users find what they are looking for easily.

Functionality cookies. These are used to recognize you when you return to our website. This enables us to personalize our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).

Targeting cookies. These cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We will use this information to make our website and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests. We may also share this information with third parties for this purpose.

You can find more information about the individual cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them below.

**First-party (IT Governance Ltd) cookies**

This website will set some cookies that are essential for the website to operate correctly. These cookies, none of which capture personally identifiable information, are as follows:

Visitor ID – this cookie is a numeric value that identifies unique visitors and provides coherence and consistency to a site visit;  
Page Number – this cookie identifies the page you are on;  
Session ID – this cookie identifies your website session;  
Test – this cookie checks whether or not your browser supports cookies; Order – this cookie ensures that your shopping basket works correctly.

**Third-party cookies**

Our websites will set several types of third-party cookie, and we do not control the operation of any of them. The third-party cookies which may be set include:

Google Analytics – we use Google Analytics to collect data about website usage. This data does not include personally identifiable information. You can view the Google Privacy Policy here: http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.

AddThis – the AddThis cookie is used when you use the ShareThis service on our website to share a link with LinkedIn, Facebook, Twitter, etc. You can read the AddThis Privacy Policy here: http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy.

Facebook Pixels – we use Facebook Pixels to retarget website users for Facebook ads. This means that if you browse our website, you’re more likely to see our Facebook ads. You can view the Privacy Policy here: https://www.facebook.com/policy.php

CommentLuv – we use CommentLuv to give blog commenters the option to include a link to one of their recent blog posts with their comment. This data improves the users experience. You can opt out of using CommentLuv when posting your comments. For more information on this privacy policy contact the developer here: https://wordpress.org/plugins/commentluv/‹

Mailchimp– we use Mailchimp to collect names and email addresses when offering upgraded content in blog posts. This gives us the opportunity to continue to send out content to those people who signed up. This is always a double opt-in option. You can find Mailchimp Privacy Policy here: https://www.leadpages.net/privacy

Askimet – we use Askimet to block spam comments. It’s a plug-in that blocks suspicious comments (including suspicious IP addresses) so that we don’t have to spend huge chunks of time deleting spam comments. You can view their terms of service right here: https://akismet.com/tos/

**Amazon Affiliates** – we use Amazon Affiliates to provide a means for our site to earn advertising fees. You can find their privacy policy here: https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html

You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of our site.
